{
    "Party": [
        {"question":"diss sicken ate it rife her","hint":"The real MVP tonight","answer":"Designated Driver","description":"The only double D’s who will let you in their car"},
        {"question":"hug cup called sure","hint":"Sleeping around","answer":"Hookup Culture","description":"Another way of saying one night stands are in and catching feelings is out"},
        {"question":"par grr all","hint":"On to the next","answer":"Bar Crawl","description":"Binge drinking but in an organized fashion"},
        {"question":"stirrup oak her","hint":"Naked games","answer":"Strip Poker","description":"The only form of gambling where you can literally lose the shirt off your back"},
        {"question":"fizz dub hum bing","hint":"Clubbing","answer":"Fist Pumping","description":"The fraternity bro official dance move"},
        {"question":"hog tote bear vest","hint":"Bier","answer":"Oktoberfest","description":"A month long excuse to get drunk"},
        {"question":"shale low shods","hint":"Dessert drink","answer":"Jello Shots","description":"Kid snack for adults"},
        {"question":"alt drum use ick vest if full","hint":"Electronic beats","answer":"Ultra Music Festival","description":"Heaven for fist pumpers"},
        {"question":"due rug tess","hint":"Pee cup","answer":"Drug Test","description":"Description: A multiple choice exam about drugs and their history"},
        {"question":"graph tub here","hint":"Not Bud Light","answer":"Craft Beer","description":"An expensive alternative for pinky up beer drinkers"},
        {"question":"spend tub ought all","hint":"Kiss kiss","answer":"Spin The Bottle","description":"A classic tactic to kiss your middle school crush"},
        {"question":"bro jet aisle phon mitten","hint":"Passion puke","answer":"Projectile Vomiting","description":"Pretty normal puking, except double the airtime"},
        {"question":"sunned ace carries","hint":"Hungover","answer":"Sunday Scaries","description":"“I’m never gonna drink again” (riiiiiiight)"},
        {"question":"kay gust ands","hint":"Tap it","answer":"Keg Stands","description":"Doing a handstand while guzzling alcohol directly from the tap"},
        {"question":"mails drip her","hint":"Dollar bills","answer":"Male Stripper","description":"Plays 'Pony' by Ginuwine"},
        {"question":"pain yuck hole odd huh","hint":"Pineapple punch","answer":"Piña Colada","description":"A dessert in the form of an alcoholic beverage"},
        {"question":"sog key pom","hint":"Beer cocktail","answer":"Sake Bomb","description":"A mixed drink of sake and beer that must be consumed in one go"},
        {"question":"met tickle mayor won huh","hint":"Anxiety","answer":"Medical Marijuana","description":"How to get your weed covered by insurance"},
        {"question":"paw where our","hint":"Beer timer","answer":"Power Hour","description":"A drinking challenge in which you take a shot of beer every minute for an hour"},
        {"question":"tab pith hug egg","hint":"Pour the beer","answer":"Tap The Keg","description":"To prepare a keg for the dispensing of its wondrous contents"},
        {"question":"pod tum mull his minnows us","hint":"Brunch","answer":"Bottomless Mimosas","description":"The only requirement when looking for a place to have brunch"},
        {"question":"read bow fog caw","hint":"Classic combo","answer":"Red Bull Vodka","description":"For when your body’s too tired to party but your friends convince you to come out"},
        {"question":"tech heel huts hot","hint":"Lots of lime","answer":"Tequila Shot","description":"A real life crisis when there’s no salt or lime available"},
        {"question":"bee her bong","hint":"Collegiate sport","answer":"Beer Pong","description":"The rules may change from party to party but the getting drunk part stays the same"},
        {"question":"past hutch owe ain’t","hint":"Split the pot","answer":"Pass The Joint","description":"The communal sharing of a marijuana cigarette"},
        {"question":"way camp ache","hint":"Off to a good start","answer":"Wake And Bake","description":"The Cali way to start your day"},
        {"question":"trunk cog holes","hint":"Tipsy eyes","answer":"Drunk Goggles","description":"When you wake up, roll over and realize, 'What the heck was I thinking?'"},
        {"question":"half dare bar tee","hint":"Round 2","answer":"After Party","description":"The party for the people who were too cool for the party"},
        {"question":"bought til cervix","hint":"Grey goose","answer":"Bottle Service","description":"Because waiting in line is so beneath you"},
        {"question":"foal hip cub","hint":"Red solo","answer":"Flip Cup","description":"The game you play when you get bored of beer pong"},
        {"question":"bud dish hots","hint":"Belly button","answer":"Body Shots","description":"Not recommended for people without outies"},
        {"question":"trunk eggs stink","hint":"Gibberish speaking","answer":"Drunk Texting","description":"The reason you’re waking up next to your ex"},
        {"question":"muzz comb you’ll","hint":"Russian donkey","answer":"Moscow Mule","description":"That drink you order just for the shiny copper mug"},
        {"question":"may get train","hint":"Good weather","answer":"Make It Rain","description":"Tossing $1 bills in the air like you just don’t care"},
        {"question":"seep peed he hoy you’ll","hint":"'For anxiety'","answer":"CBD Oil","description":"A marijuana leaf extract that supposedly cures everything"},
        {"question":"barrel limp picks","hint":"Local competition","answer":"Beer Olympics","description":"A series of competitive events devised as a way to get all your friends blasted"},
        {"question":"hank oaf irk your","hint":"Sunday medication","answer":"Hangover Cure","description":"Any concoction used to mitigate the symptoms of last night’s partying"},
        {"question":"pinch shrink gang","hint":"Dedicated hydration","answer":"Binge Drinking","description":"The surest way to find yourself waking up in a strange place sometime later"},
        {"question":"hids fie folk logs hum aware","hint":"Time to drink","answer":"It’s 5 o’clock somewhere","description":"An excuse to start drinking whenever you want"},
        {"question":"par dave owl","hint":"Socially unacceptable ","answer":"Party Foul","description":"Anything that wastes intoxicants or ruins the mood"},
        {"question":"tea ages he","hint":"Hippie chemistry ","answer":"THC","description":"The sweet sauce in weed that gets you lit"},
        {"question":"shod gone ink appear","hint":"Quick drink","answer":"Shotgunning A Beer","description":"A competitive drinking activity no one actually enjoys but that is done to prove basic biological abilities"},
        {"question":"pod pro niece","hint":"Chill chocolate","answer":"Pot Brownies","description":"A munchy that gives you the munchies"},
        {"question":"hearts celts or","hint":"Fizzy","answer":"Hard Seltzer","description":"Low calorie intoxication"},
        {"question":"room manned coat","hint":"Classic combo","answer":"Rum And Coke","description":"The safe choice for when you never go out but want to seem cool"},
        {"question":"mark car eat duh","hint":"Salty rim","answer":"Margarita","description":"Sugar rim is better than salt and that’s proven by science"},
        {"question":"peer belle he","hint":"Too much bud","answer":"Beer Belly","description":"Self inflicted male pregnancy"},
        {"question":"ease zig are wet","hint":"Juul","answer":"E-Cigarette","description":"Like Diet Coke, modified enough to make you think you’re making a healthy decision"},
        {"question":"dare team art teenie","hint":"Not clean","answer":"Dirty Martini","description":"A drink for when you’re feeling equal parts fancy and naughty"},
        {"question":"app he yeah war","hint":"Joyous time","answer":"Happy Hour","description":"When the least appetizing foods and drinks are sold at a steep discount to clear up kitchen space"},
        {"question":"bob pin bought tolls","hint":"Champagne","answer":"Poppin’ Bottles","description":"The process of opening and consuming large quantities of alcohol"},
        {"question":"fay guy tee","hint":"Golden ticket","answer":"Fake ID","description":"McLovin’s driver’s license"},
        {"question":"jane’s moat king","hint":"Lotta butts","answer":"Chain Smoking","description":"The act of smoking one cigarette after another until you’ve run out of money or oxygen"},
        {"question":"bogs due i’m","hint":"Franzia","answer":"Boxed Wine","description":"Cheap but gets the job done"},
        {"question":"cram pear heave ought caw","hint":"Spiked juice","answer":"Cranberry Vodka","description":"Delicious and helps to fight off UTI’s"},
        {"question":"ball hack doubt","hint":"Drunken darkness","answer":"Blacked Out","description":"An indication that you probably should’ve stopped a couple shots ago"},
        {"question":"bod dull hope inner","hint":"Cork","answer":"Bottle Opener","description":"A tool used to open bottles"},
        {"question":"napper half fie heifer","hint":"Secrets told","answer":"Never Have I Ever","description":"A game useful for finding out things about your friends you wish you hadn’t"},
        {"question":"drub bet lie kits sot","hint":"Snoooop","answer":"Drop It Like It’s Hot","description":"A command typically issued to a woman with motherly hips"},
        {"question":"can ebb hiss","hint":"Like MJ","answer":"Cannabis","description":"The scientific name for a marijuana plant that no one uses in conversation"},
        {"question":"ha tub ox sing","hint":"Foggy car","answer":"Hot Boxing","description":"Utilizing the airtight nature of a car to obtain and maintain optimal bakedness"},
        {"question":"hid tub pong","hint":"Big toke","answer":"Hit The Bong","description":"Taking a large pull from your favorite smoke-up device"},
        {"question":"merry one nah","hint":"Lazy leaf","answer":"Marijuana","description":"Nature’s gift to mankind"},
        {"question":"wad herb pong","hint":"Purified smoke","answer":"Water Bong","description":"A large pipe often responsible for tricking smokers into thinking they’re inhaling 'purified smoke'"},
        {"question":"got hem out","hint":"Need water","answer":"Cotton Mouth","description":"When your mouth is drier than the Sahara but you’re still lighting up"},
        {"question":"moan cheese","hint":"Hangry","answer":"Munchies","description":"An intense desire to eat junk food, often as a symptom of marijuana usage"},
        {"question":"thirds teeth or stay","hint":"Not TGIF","answer":"Thirsty Thursday","description":"Why wait till the weekend to get sloppy drunk?"},
        {"question":"pup of bass","hint":"Joint instructions","answer":"Puff Puff Pass","description":"What you say when someone is hogging the blunt"},
        {"question":"ford went he","hint":"National holiday","answer":"4/20","description":"A great time for a great time"},
        {"question":"read soul oak up","hint":"Beer pong","answer":"Red Solo Cup","description":"A college commodity"},
        {"question":"duh hay trink inn","hint":"Sunny sip","answer":"Day Drinking","description":"Because why wait ‘til the sun goes down?"},
        {"question":"curls nuh eye doubt","hint":"Ladies only","answer":"Girls Night Out","description":"Early 20’s: wild\nAny age after then: charcuterie boards and wine."},
        {"question":"furl oak hoe","hint":"Banned substance","answer":"Four Loko","description":"The cheapest way to black out and get wired out of your mind at the same time"}
    ],
    "Kinky": [
        {"question":"g1q1","hint":"g1h1","answer":"g1a1"},
        {"question":"g1q2","hint":"g1h2","answer":"g1a2"},
        {"question":"g1q3","hint":"g1h3","answer":"g1a3"},
        {"question":"g1q4","hint":"g1h4","answer":"g1a4"},
        {"question":"g1q5","hint":"g1h5","answer":"g1a5"},
        {"question":"g1q6","hint":"g1h6","answer":"g1a6"},
        {"question":"g1q7","hint":"g1h7","answer":"g1a7"},
        {"question":"g1q8","hint":"g1h8","answer":"g1a8"},
        {"question":"g1q9","hint":"g1h9","answer":"g1a9"},
        {"question":"g1q10","hint":"g1h10","answer":"g1a10"},
        {"question":"g1q11","hint":"g1h11","answer":"g1a11"},
        {"question":"g1q12","hint":"g1h12","answer":"g1a12"},
        {"question":"g1q13","hint":"g1h13","answer":"g1a13"},
        {"question":"g1q14","hint":"g1h14","answer":"g1a14"},
        {"question":"g1q15","hint":"g1h15","answer":"g1a15"},
        {"question":"g1q16","hint":"g1h16","answer":"g1a16"},
        {"question":"g1q17","hint":"g1h17","answer":"g1a17"},
        {"question":"g1q18","hint":"g1h18","answer":"g1a18"},
        {"question":"g1q19","hint":"g1h19","answer":"g1a19"},
        {"question":"g1q20","hint":"g1h20","answer":"g1a20"},
        {"question":"g1q21","hint":"g1h21","answer":"g1a21"},
        {"question":"g1q22","hint":"g1h22","answer":"g1a22"},
        {"question":"g1q23","hint":"g1h23","answer":"g1a23"},
        {"question":"g1q24","hint":"g1h24","answer":"g1a24"},
        {"question":"g1q25","hint":"g1h25","answer":"g1a25"},
        {"question":"g1q26","hint":"g1h26","answer":"g1a26"},
        {"question":"g1q27","hint":"g1h27","answer":"g1a27"},
        {"question":"g1q28","hint":"g1h28","answer":"g1a28"},
        {"question":"g1q29","hint":"g1h29","answer":"g1a29"},
        {"question":"g1q30","hint":"g1h30","answer":"g1a30"},
        {"question":"g1q31","hint":"g1h31","answer":"g1a31"},
        {"question":"g1q32","hint":"g1h32","answer":"g1a32"},
        {"question":"g1q33","hint":"g1h33","answer":"g1a33"},
        {"question":"g1q34","hint":"g1h34","answer":"g1a34"},
        {"question":"g1q35","hint":"g1h35","answer":"g1a35"},
        {"question":"g1q36","hint":"g1h36","answer":"g1a36"},
        {"question":"g1q37","hint":"g1h37","answer":"g1a37"},
        {"question":"g1q38","hint":"g1h38","answer":"g1a38"},
        {"question":"g1q39","hint":"g1h39","answer":"g1a39"},
        {"question":"g1q40","hint":"g1h40","answer":"g1a40"},
        {"question":"g1q41","hint":"g1h41","answer":"g1a41"},
        {"question":"g1q42","hint":"g1h42","answer":"g1a42"},
        {"question":"g1q43","hint":"g1h43","answer":"g1a43"},
        {"question":"g1q44","hint":"g1h44","answer":"g1a44"},
        {"question":"g1q45","hint":"g1h45","answer":"g1a45"},
        {"question":"g1q46","hint":"g1h46","answer":"g1a46"},
        {"question":"g1q47","hint":"g1h47","answer":"g1a47"},
        {"question":"g1q48","hint":"g1h48","answer":"g1a48"},
        {"question":"g1q49","hint":"g1h49","answer":"g1a49"},
        {"question":"g1q50","hint":"g1h50","answer":"g1a50"}
    ],
    "Pop Culture": [
        {"question":"g1q1","hint":"g1h1","answer":"g1a1"},
        {"question":"g1q2","hint":"g1h2","answer":"g1a2"},
        {"question":"g1q3","hint":"g1h3","answer":"g1a3"},
        {"question":"g1q4","hint":"g1h4","answer":"g1a4"},
        {"question":"g1q5","hint":"g1h5","answer":"g1a5"},
        {"question":"g1q6","hint":"g1h6","answer":"g1a6"},
        {"question":"g1q7","hint":"g1h7","answer":"g1a7"},
        {"question":"g1q8","hint":"g1h8","answer":"g1a8"},
        {"question":"g1q9","hint":"g1h9","answer":"g1a9"},
        {"question":"g1q10","hint":"g1h10","answer":"g1a10"},
        {"question":"g1q11","hint":"g1h11","answer":"g1a11"},
        {"question":"g1q12","hint":"g1h12","answer":"g1a12"},
        {"question":"g1q13","hint":"g1h13","answer":"g1a13"},
        {"question":"g1q14","hint":"g1h14","answer":"g1a14"},
        {"question":"g1q15","hint":"g1h15","answer":"g1a15"},
        {"question":"g1q16","hint":"g1h16","answer":"g1a16"},
        {"question":"g1q17","hint":"g1h17","answer":"g1a17"},
        {"question":"g1q18","hint":"g1h18","answer":"g1a18"},
        {"question":"g1q19","hint":"g1h19","answer":"g1a19"},
        {"question":"g1q20","hint":"g1h20","answer":"g1a20"},
        {"question":"g1q21","hint":"g1h21","answer":"g1a21"},
        {"question":"g1q22","hint":"g1h22","answer":"g1a22"},
        {"question":"g1q23","hint":"g1h23","answer":"g1a23"},
        {"question":"g1q24","hint":"g1h24","answer":"g1a24"},
        {"question":"g1q25","hint":"g1h25","answer":"g1a25"},
        {"question":"g1q26","hint":"g1h26","answer":"g1a26"},
        {"question":"g1q27","hint":"g1h27","answer":"g1a27"},
        {"question":"g1q28","hint":"g1h28","answer":"g1a28"},
        {"question":"g1q29","hint":"g1h29","answer":"g1a29"},
        {"question":"g1q30","hint":"g1h30","answer":"g1a30"},
        {"question":"g1q31","hint":"g1h31","answer":"g1a31"},
        {"question":"g1q32","hint":"g1h32","answer":"g1a32"},
        {"question":"g1q33","hint":"g1h33","answer":"g1a33"},
        {"question":"g1q34","hint":"g1h34","answer":"g1a34"},
        {"question":"g1q35","hint":"g1h35","answer":"g1a35"},
        {"question":"g1q36","hint":"g1h36","answer":"g1a36"},
        {"question":"g1q37","hint":"g1h37","answer":"g1a37"},
        {"question":"g1q38","hint":"g1h38","answer":"g1a38"},
        {"question":"g1q39","hint":"g1h39","answer":"g1a39"},
        {"question":"g1q40","hint":"g1h40","answer":"g1a40"},
        {"question":"g1q41","hint":"g1h41","answer":"g1a41"},
        {"question":"g1q42","hint":"g1h42","answer":"g1a42"},
        {"question":"g1q43","hint":"g1h43","answer":"g1a43"},
        {"question":"g1q44","hint":"g1h44","answer":"g1a44"},
        {"question":"g1q45","hint":"g1h45","answer":"g1a45"},
        {"question":"g1q46","hint":"g1h46","answer":"g1a46"},
        {"question":"g1q47","hint":"g1h47","answer":"g1a47"},
        {"question":"g1q48","hint":"g1h48","answer":"g1a48"},
        {"question":"g1q49","hint":"g1h49","answer":"g1a49"},
        {"question":"g1q50","hint":"g1h50","answer":"g1a50"}

    ]

}
